[
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 14 + 4 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "22",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "20",
        "22",
        "27"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 13 + 9 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "58",
      "options": [
        "63",
        "56",
        "58",
        "60"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 20 + 1 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "27",
        "30",
        "23",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 7 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "30",
      "options": [
        "32",
        "30",
        "28",
        "35"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 4 + 4 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "24",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "24",
        "29",
        "26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 1 + 7 \u00d7 1?",
      "correctAnswer": "8",
      "options": [
        "10",
        "13",
        "8",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 7 + 9 \u00d7 2?",
      "correctAnswer": "25",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "30",
        "27",
        "25"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 18 + 8 \u00d7 8?",
      "correctAnswer": "82",
      "options": [
        "80",
        "82",
        "84",
        "87"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 9 + 5 \u00d7 6?",
      "correctAnswer": "39",
      "options": [
        "39",
        "37",
        "44",
        "41"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the result <br> of 16 + 3 \u00d7 5?",
      "correctAnswer": "31",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "31",
        "29",
        "36"
      ]
    }
]